

# Tom Kodesh

Linux Systems Administrator

### **About Me**

Hello! I'm Tom Kodesh. I am passionate about Linux and Linux systems. A skilled Linux engineer with demonstrated experience configuring, managing and supporting a variety of enterprise Linux server applications and services. I am a quick learner and a team player that can capitalize on the strengths of others while sharing my own strengths to maximize productivity and timely deliverables.

### **Professional Skills**

HTML MASTER CSS EXPERT **JavaScript** ADVANCE **WordPress** ADVANCE **Adobe Photoshop** MASTER Adobe Illustrator EXPERT Sketch EXPERT Adobe XD BEGINNER

## Work Experience

O Linux Systems Operations Administrator III at Rackspace Technology

2011 - 2021

Electronic Data Interchange Analyst / Developer at Justin Brands Inc

2006 - 2011

- O Systems Administrator / Repair Technician at MetroPC 2005 2006
- Unix/Linux System Administrator at Propagation Networks2004 2005
- Linux Operations Administrator at Kenneth Copeland Ministries
   2003 2004

## Education

O Associate of Arts and Sciences in Networked Systems
Administration from Westwood College

2005 - 2006

Graduated with a 3.93 GPA

Associate in Criminal Justice and Law Enforcement Administration from Odessa College

1990 - 1991

Graduated with 3.81 GPA

#### References



Joe

Technical Support Manager at Rackspace

Tom Kodesh is a high performing individual with self-discipline and self-motivation as a personal driver. I would add Tom to my team if the opportunity presented it's self again. His knowledge as a Linux Engineer exceeds many of his peers and he still works with those needing to bridge their OS knowledge gaps. A true team player and an asset to any team that takes him on-board.



Mark

Maintenance Team Linux System Administrator at Rackspace

Tom is a great asset and all-star to any team! Highly motivated, knowledgeable, and self discipled. When a question or issue arose I did not hesitate to ask Tom for assistance as he is very approachable and willing to help.



Ben

Linux Enterprise Support Engineer at Rackspace

Very good Linux skills. Great coworker in general. A good asset on any team.



Micah

VMware Technical Support Manager at Rackspace

Tom is an invaluable resource to any team. I've had the pleasure of working with Tom over the years in a technical and leadership capacity. His willingness to dive in and collaborate has helped drive unique solutions and develop those around him.



Linux System Administrator at Rackspace

It is my distinct pleasure to wholeheartedly recommend Tom. In the four years that I have worked with him, Tom has been both mentor and colleague. Tom is always willing to go the extra mile on behalf of our customers. He is among the hardest workers I have ever known. His Linux skills are formidable, and he is happy to share his knowledge with others. Any organization would be supremely lucky to count Tom among its ranks.